litespeedtech.com 2015-02-15

# Privacy Policy - LiteSpeed Tech

## Lite Speed Technologies Privacy Policy

Lite Speed Technologies is committed to protecting your privacy. This policy ("Privacy Policy" or "Policy") explains our practices for our site, www.litespeedtech.com ("Site"). Your can visit most pages of the Site without giving us any information about yourself, but sometimes we do need information to provide services that you request. By using this Site or any products or services provided through the Site, you expressly consent to the use and disclosure of information as described in this Privacy Policy. Lite Speed Technologies may periodically update this Privacy Policy. Lite Speed Technologies encourages you to review this Privacy Policy periodically for any changes. IF YOU DO NOT AGREE WITH ANY OF THE TERMS BELOW, YOU SHOULD NOT USE THIS SITE OR THE PRODUCTS OR SERVICES OFFERED BY LITE SPEED TECHNOLOGIES AT THIS SITE.

**Collection & Use of Personal Information**  
We will ask your for certain personal information when you complete registration or product information request forms on the Site, including but not limited to your name, address, telephone number, email address, and credit card information. You can always choose not to provide us with the requested information, however, you may not be able to complete the transaction or use our products or services if you do not provide the information requested.

We use your personal information to respond to your requests, or provide you with information regarding our products, services, partners, and company. Lite Speed will only disclose your personal information to third parties if acting under a good faith belief that such action is necessary, including but not limited to: (a) to resolve disputes, investigate problems, or comply with laws or regulations; (b) to enforce our Terms of Service; (c) to protect and defend the rights, property, or safety of our company or our users; or (d) in the event of a merger, acquisition or sale of all or substantially all Lite Speed Technologies' assets. Other than this limited activity, we do not share, sell or rent any personal information to third parties.

You will receive notice in the form of modifications to this Policy when information about you might go to third parties other than as described in this Policy, and you always have the opportunity to contact us as set forth below if you do not wish your information to go to third parties.

**Security**  
We use reasonable security methods to protect your personal information from unauthorized access, use or disclosure. No data transmission over the Internet or any wireless network can be guaranteed to be perfectly secure. While we try to protect your personal information, we cannot guarantee the security of any information you transmit to us, and you do so at your own risk.  
Lite Speed Technologies uses industry-standard SSL-encryption to protect sensitive data.

**Cookies**  
"Cookies" are small pieces of information that your browser stores on your computer on behalf of a web site that you have visited. Cookies may be used in order to complete transactions on our site. You can always choose not to accept cookies with the settings of your web browser, however, you may not be able to complete these transactions if you do not accept cookies.

**Contact Us**   
If you would like to update information that you have voluntarily provided to us, stop receiving information from us, or if you have any questions about the Privacy Policy or Site, please e-mail [info@litespeedtech.com](mailto:info@litespeedtech.com).
